Wadsworth Family Papers 1790-1950
Wadsworth Family Papers
- Persons Who Worked for the Wadsworths as Farm or Day Laborers, 1831-1842; 5 ledgers
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, April, 12 1841-June 9, 1841:; D (Box unwrapped)
Derby and Farnham, New York City clothiers, Bill January 14, 1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Clothing: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Clothing Sh 27
Dewey, George (1837-1917) Admiral Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin English Club; accepts invitation; list of guests. Box LWAW2 F8 Shelf 26
Dobbin, H W Lt. Col. 102 Regimental Infantry, Letter to September 14, 1815. Wadsworth,William (1761-1833) Militia discipline. Bk 61 P 9 Shelf 27
Donelson, Andrew Jackson (1799-1871) Diplomat Letter from Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Douglas, Catherine Horticulturist, Letter from January 31, 1831 Wadsworth,William Wolcott England; Plants. Box L1 Folder 2 Sh 15
Driggs, Laurence (1876-1945) Colonial Airlines List of stockholders 4/7/1928 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Airlines; Colonial Western Airways. Box J112E F 1
Duvall, W A Clerk to Senator James, and others Letters (5) 1926-1928 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Wadsworth Family History; General James S., etc. Box J112E F 32sh 59
Dyer, George Carrol (b. 1898) Pub. of "The Censor, Letters to and from (3) 1931 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics; Candidacy for President. Box J112D F 3 Sh 59
Eagle Hotel, Rochester NY Bill May 20, 1841. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Eagle Tavern Rochester NY Bills (4) 1840 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Bar bill and stable, Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotel Shelf 27
Eagle Tavern Albany NY Bills (2) 1841. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Elders, Church of Geneseo, Letter to June, 1819 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Church Glebe lot improvement;Profit to the Church. Bk 61 P 544 Shelf 27
Election Registrars Vote tallies (5) 1914-1926 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Election results. Box J112E F 31 Sh 59
Eliot, Samuel (1821-1898) Trinity College Pres. Letter from Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Wadsworth, Wm. Austin, His college education. Box LEAW1 F 17 Shelf 23
Ellicott, Joseph (1756-1826) Holland Purchase Letter to November 20, 1817 Wadsworth,James (1768-i844) Counties: Objection to subdivision of Genesee and Ontario. Bk 61 P 292 Shelf 27
Emott, James (1771-1850) State legislator, Canandaigua NY, Letter to February 29, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Genesee Valley lands in 1806. Bk 61 P 63 Shelf 27
Erie County Nursery, Buffalo NY, Bill October 16, 1838 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Fruit tree orders, Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Gardens Shelf 27
Famaris, Robert New York City merchant, Bill February 1,1840 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Clothing: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Clothing Sh 27
Farley, James Aloysius (1888-1976) Postmaster General, Letters to and from (2) 1934 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Postmaster appointment for Perry. Box J112D F 4 Sh 59
Farmer, William Clerk and farm manager in Ohio, Letters to and from 1830's. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Farm news; Ohio news. Use calendars in Box L1 Shelf 15
Farmer, William Clerk and farm manager in Ohio Letters from (6) 1831-1832 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Ohio lands. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Farnham, Heman Blacksmith, Accounts with 1842. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Blacksmith services for Wadsworth farms April -November. Box AW1 Book B Shelf 3
Farrol, J M S Blvd Hausmann, Paris France, Letter from December 9, 1884. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. Box LEAW1 F 18 Shelf 23
Faulkner, James Settler and miller in Dansville, Letters from (2) 1841 Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Milling. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Fellows, Joseph and Thomas Ludlow Ogden, the Ogden Company, Letter to December 6, 1838. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Number of Chiefs signing. Box LBk 1 P 44 Sh 27
Fellows, Joseph, Pulteney agent; Ogden Company partner, Letters from (2) 1839. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Indian lands in Buffalo Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Fellows, Joseph, Pulteney agent; Ogden Company partner, Letters to (32) October 7, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Pulteney Estate land accounts. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Felton, Cornelius Conway (1807-1862) Educator, Letters from (6) 1827-1829. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Temple Hill Academy. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Finch, Vere, Clarendon TX, Letters to and from (2) 1915. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Neutral Shipping with England in World War I. Box J112E F 23 Sh 59
Fish, Edith Livingston, Garrison NY, Letters from (17) 1879-82. Wadsworth,William Austin Personal. Box LWAW2 F 12 Shelf 26
Fitzhugh, Daniel H Sonyea settler; Estate Manager, Letters from (77) 1853-1866. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Family business. William Wolcott's estate. Box LMisc3 Shelf 24
Fitzhugh, Daniel H Sonyea settler; Estate Manager, Letters to (50+) 1848-1867. Wadsworth family Family business: William Wolcott's estate. Boxes L 5-11 Shelf 16
Fitzhugh, Daniel H Sonyea settler; Estate Manager, Letter from 3/27/1865. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Flood of 1865, Damage to river valley properties Box LMisc3 F Flood Sh24
Flagg, Azariah Cutting (1790-1873) Editor; State officer Letter from 3/8/1850. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Fletcher, Henry P (1873-1954) Chair Republican Nat Com, Letters from (2) 1934. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics; Republican Party. Box J112D F 6 Sh 59
Floyd, Margaret Henderson and others; Architectural historians, Letters from, etc. (15) 1976-1987. Wadsworth,William Perkins Homestead research on enlargement and renovation. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Folsom, Gilman Letter to April 24, 1817. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Cattle sale of oxen and calves. Bk 61 P 217 Shelf 27
Foot, Belinda York tenant and land owner, Bill of Sale 2 copies 1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott York land. Box C1 Fold. 25 Shelf 9
Forman, Abraham, 1st Pastor 2nd Presbyterian Church, Geneseo, Letter to April 28, 1817. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Minister in Geneseo; Gospel society's call to Forman. Bk 61 P 270 Shelf 27
Forty Thousand Acre Tract; Chili and Gates townships, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Forty Thousand Acre Tract Lots. Map File #1 Main Set
Fraser, Samuel (1876-1959) Horticulturist in Geneseo, Documents (3 folders) 1913 and previous records. Wadsworth,William Austin Fruit tree project; Fall Brook farm. File Cab. 1, Drawer 2
Fry, James B (1827-1894) Army officer, author Letter from 10/20/1861. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs.
Fuller, Philo Case (1787-1855) 1st family clerk, Letters from (7) 1830-1839. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Michigan lands. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Fuller, Philo Case (1787-1855) 1st family clerk, Letter to September 29, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Michigan lands; deed in Kalamazoo. Box LBk 1 P 33 Sh 27
Garbutt, William, Miner of gypsum in Wheatland, Letter to July 29, 1835. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Gypsum; "plaster" to be sent to Benjamin Joy in Toledo Box LBk 1 p 66 Shelf 27
Garratt, William, New York City wool trader and merchant, Letter to July 6, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; three years shear for sale. Bk 61 P 406 Shelf 27
Gates township, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Gates settlers and land owners. Map File #1 Main Set
Gates, Horatio and Nephew Montreal merchants and exporters, Letters to (5) 1817-1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Trade with Canada, etc. Bk 61 Use index Shelf 7
Gates, Horatio and Nephew, Montreal merchants and exporters, Letter to January 24, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Trade with Great Britain thru Canada; Erie Canal. Bk 61 P 314 Shelf 27
Gates, Oliver, Ogden settler, Letter to September 12, 1815. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) School House lot for Ogden. Bk 61 P 6 Shelf 27
Genesee Valley Hunt Club, Documents (17 folders) 1887-1916. Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt Club Letters, Lists, Programs; See Also Regrets Box LWAW6 Shelf 26
Geneseo High School, Committee report. Wadsworth,William Wolcott School examinations. File cabinet 1 Drawer 2
Geneseo Normal School, Correspondence (5) 1887. Wadsworth,William Austin Normal School prizes; spring bulbs for science dept. File cabinet 1 Drawer 2
Geneseo School Districts, Income distribution, 1868. Wadsworth, Charles F. School income for each district. File cabinet 1 Drawer 2
Geneseo township and Village, Maps 19th century Wadsworth,James S (180'-1864) Geneseo settlers and landowners; Village plans as it grew. Map File #1 Main Set
Gillet, Ransom Hooker (1800-1876) US Com. 1838 Treaty, Letter to September 28, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838. Box LBk 1 P 40 Sh 27
Gillet, Ransom Hooker (1800-1876) US Com. 1838 Treaty, Letter to October 2, 1838. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Convening the council of Chiefs. Box LBk 1 P 35 Sh 27
Gilpin, Henry Dilworth (1801-1860) Attorney General, Letter from 11/5/1839. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Globe Hotel, New York city, Bill March 19, 1841 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
Good, James W (1866-1929) Secretary of War, Letter from 1929. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Personal. Box J112D F 7 Sh 59
Goodyear, Charles W. (1846-1911) Buffalo NY attorney, Letter from 8/29/1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Airline competition; Buffalo Airways. Box J112E F 1
Gordon, Zery, Blacksmith, Bill 1838. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Blacksmith services. Examples of vouchers' scope, Box V1 Blacksmith Sh 27
Grabau, Amadeus William (1870-1946) Geologist, Letter to Edward Hall 1907. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Genesee River Flood Control Dam plans above Portage. Box J112E F 13 Sh 59
Granger, Francis (1792-1868) Whig Politician, Letters from (2) 1841-1843. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Grant, Joseph (1858-1942) Undersecretary of State, Letter from 1926. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Treaty with Turkey. Box J112E F 30 Sh 59
Grant, Ulysses, President and Mexican Southern RR Co. Letter from September 10, 1881. Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt. Box LWAW2 F 17 Shelf 26
Grant, William (1804-1887) Moscow NY, Letter from July 27, 1887. Wadsworth,William Austin Hounds to be delivered. See Also subject heading "Hunt." Box LWAW2 F 18 Shelf 26
Greece township, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Greece Settlers and land owners. Map File #1 Main Set
Griffith, E M Forester, Working plan, October 1889. Wadsworth,Wadsworth family Forestation of their estate. Wads SD 387 W6 G7
Griswold, Frank Gray (1854-1937) Merchant and sportsman, Letters from (5) 1880-1885. Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt. Box LWAW2 F 21 Shelf 26
Guerney, E M (1854-1937) Cambridge MA, Letter from Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Wadsworth, Wm. Austin, His college education. Box LEAW1 F 19 Shelf 23
Guernsey, James K Lima NY, Letters to (2) Feb 7, 1816; Nov 19, 1817. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Counties: Objection to subdivision of Genesee and Ontario. Bk 61 P 50, 291 sh 27
Hagner, Peter (1772-1850) US War Department Accountant, Letter to February 17, 1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) War of 1812; sick soldiers cared for by Poor Master Bk 61 P 498 Shelf 27
Harding, William H Syracuse NY, and others, Letters (5) 1925-1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Senate Rules re seating of new members. Box J112E F 38 Sh 59
Hartford House in Geneseo, built by General James S., Inventory (1 folder) 190? Wadsworth,James Wolcott Jr. Hartford House, furnishings. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Harwood, Lizzie, Cocleton, England, Letters from (2) 1884-1885. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal; Church and religious matters. Box LEAW1 F 21 Shelf 23
Hawkes, Cephas, Woolen mill proprietor, Geneva, Letter to September 20. 1815. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; Notes due. Bk 61 P 11 Shelf 27
Hazleton, Henry I Chesborough Seminary, Chili NY, Letter from 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. North Chili Post office proposed name West Rochester. Box J112E F 36 Sh 59
Henrietta township, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James and James S Henrietta settlers and land owners. Map file, Both sets
Hicock, S Rae, (1883-1945) Mens' Jewelry Co., Rochester NY, Letter from 7/28/1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Airline stock. Box J112E F 1
Hillard. George Stillman (1808-1879) Lawyer and author, Letters from (3) 1828-1841. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Hogmire, Daniel Hand Henry Hogmire, settlers in Avon Lease 1838. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Geneseo land. Box C1 Fold. 14 Shelf 9
Holland Purchase. Map 19th century Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Holland Purchase Tracts Copy of the Ellicott original. Map file, Both sets
Hollenbeck, F and D K, Ohio agents, Sale sign 1871. Wadsworth estate Ohio lands in Liberty, Wood County. Map file Drawer 20
Holly, Myron (Holley) (1749-1841) Reformer; Canal Com. Letter to March 18, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Bridge at Avon; tolls; State Road; proposed canals. Bk 61 P 77 Shelf 27
Holly, Myron (Holley) (1749-1841) Reformer; Canal Com. Letter to February 11. 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Libraries; Clergy; Agriculture; Gov Clinton's speech Bk 61 P 325 Shelf 27
Holmes. Oliver Wendell, Sr. (1809-1894) Author. doctor. Letters from (4) 1874 and undated. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Poetry she had given to him, etc. Box LEAW1 Fs 22,23 Sh23
Homestead in Geneseo. Built by James (1768-1844). Bills (2 folders) 1853-1898. Wadsworth,Emmeline and William A. Gardener's orders for seed and nursery stock. File Cab. I. Drawer 2
Homestead in Geneseo. Built by James (1768-1844), Inventory 190? Wadsworth,William Austin Homestead furnishings. File Cab. I. Drawer 2
Homestead in Geneseo, Built by James (1768-1844). Documents (2 folders) 1874-1875. Wadsworth,William Austin Homestead moved. File Cab. I, Drawer 2
Homestead in Geneseo. Built by James (1768-1844). Cost estimates 1870. Wadsworth,William Austin Homestead moved. File Cab. I. Drawer 2
Homestead in Geneseo. Built by James (1768-1844), Documents (8 folders) 1864-1902. Wadsworth,Emmeline and William A Homestead repairs and renovations. File Cab. I. Drawer 2
Hoover. Herbert (1874-1964) 31st President of US. Letters from (2) 1927 and 1931. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Personal; American Chemical Society Prize. Box J112D F 8 Sh 59
Hopkins. Samuel M • Founded Moscow village; Writer, Letter to January 10. 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Counties: Objection to subdivision of Genesee and Ontario. Bk 61 P 308 Shelf 27
Hornaday, William Temple (1854-1937) Zoologist and Author, Letters to M. Grant(2) 1912. Wadsworth,William Austin Gun collection; Daniel Boone rifle;Boone and Crockett Club Box LWAW2 F 30 Shelf 26
Hotchkiss, William Horace (1864-1950) National Progressive Party, Letters from (3) 1912. Wadsworth,William Austin Politics; Progressive Party endorsement for Chairman. Box LWAW2 F 31 Shelf 26
Howe, Walter Bruce (1879-1954) Washington Attorney, Documents (4) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Wadsworth Estate. Box J112E F 33 Sh 59
Howland family, Mount Morris, New York, Letters from (16) 1881-1895. Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt; County Fair. Box LWAW2 Fs 33-35 Sh26
Hubbell, Levi (1808-1876) Canandaigua Jurist, Letters from (3) 1829-1830. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Business matters. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Hudson, Henry, Hartford CT, Agent for Daniel Wadsworth, Letters to (31) September 21, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; Morris Tract etc. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Humphrey and Hull, New York Merchants, Letters to (23) 1815-1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Sheep; Wine and other merchandise orders. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Hungerford, Orville (1790-1851) Congressman, Letter from 5/5/1844. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Hunt, Richard Morris (1828-95) Architect, and workmen, Plans and bills (26) 1887-1888. Wadsworth,William Austin Fountain in Geneseo, construction and materials. File Cab. 1, Drawer 2
Hutchinson, J Cleveland OH, Letter to June 1, 1836. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Michigan lands; Kalamazoo and St. Joseph Counties Box LBk 1 P 4 Sh 27
Hutton, Isaac and G Merchants, 15 Court St., Albany, Letters to (10) September 16, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-i844) Wool; orders for goods; bills, etc. Bk 61.Sh 27 use index
Hutton, Isaac, Merchant, 15 Court st., Albany, Letter to September 12, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Woolen mills; orders for Communion Plate and Fireplace Bk 61 P 149 Shelf 27
Inches, Henderson, Jr., Business agent in Boston; Nephew, Letters from 1830-1850. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Business matters; Family news from Boston. Box L1-L5 See Calendars
Inches, Henderson, Jr., Business agent in Boston; Nephew, Letters from (3) 1833-1838. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Family and Business. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Inches, Henderson, Jr., Business agent in Boston; Nephew, Balance sheet May 7, 1838 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Wool; Sale and Purchases. Example of Inches services, Box V1 Inches Shelf 27
Jackson, Andrew (1767-1845) 7th US President, Letters Patent (21) 1835. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Michigan lands. Box CM2 Shelf 14
Jacobs, Benjamin, Boston, MA merchant, Bills (3) 1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Linen and Table cloths: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Household Sh 27
Janes, Nelson (1819-1899) Agent for Estate of James S., Letters from (2) Wadsworth,William Austin Family business. Box LWAW2 F 41 Shelf 26
Janes, Nelson (1819-1899) Agent"for Estate of James S., Letters to (42) 1878-1880. Wadsworth,William Austin Family business. Box L17 Shelf 17
Janes, Nelson (1819-1899) Agent for Estate of James S., Letters to and from (50+) 1864-1870. Wadsworth,Nancy W. Rodgers Family business. Box J97 Shelf 55A
Johnson, Wayne (1892-1947) Attorney, Documents (2) Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Constitutional Amendments. Box J112E F 6 Sh 59
Johnson, Wayne (1892-1947) Attorney, Brief 1932 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Constitutional Amendments. Box J112E F 6 Shelf 59
Johnston, John White Monroe County Fish and Game Assoc., Letters from (3) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Bird Sanctuary in Avon; Canada Geese. Box J112E F 3 Sh 59
Jones, Beatrice (1872-1959) Landscape architect, Letters from, etc.(2 ) 1900. Wadsworth,William Austin Geneseo Park. See in reference books under Farrand. File Cab. 1, Drawer 2
Jones, Horatio (1769-1836) Indian fighter and interpreter, Letter to January 12, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Indian Missionary, Rev. Ely introduced. Bk 61 P 309 Shelf 27
Jones, Horatio, Early Genesee Valley settler, Letter from 2/16/1838. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Indian affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Jones, Spencer Cone (1836-1915) Lawyer and Banker, Letters from (3) Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. Box LEAW1 F 24 Shelf 23
Joy, Benjamin, Family agent in Ohio and Michigan, Letter to April 18, 1835. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Cattle: Instructions for purchasing. Box LBk 1 P 21 Shelf 27
Joy, Benjamin, Family agent in Ohio and Michigan, Lease October 22, 1840 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Ohio lands in Sylvania, Ohio; five year lease. Box C1 Joy folder Sh 9
Joy, Benjamin, Family agent in Ohio and Michigan, Letters to (36) 1830-1050. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-William Farmer (Book 58)
Ohio lands; Michigan lands. Box LBk 1 Sh 27-indexed
Joy, Benjamin, Family agent in Ohio and Michigan, Letters from and to 1830-1850. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-William Farmer,
Ohio lands; Sales and farm news. Box L1-L5 See Calendars
Keating, John, Agent for Six family lands, Letter to August 27, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Daughters; Parenting. Bk 61 P 426 Shelf 27
Keating, John, Agent for Six family lands, Lists of settlers July 6, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Henrietta settlers and Riga settlers on C.C. Six lands. Bk 61 P 446-52 Shelf 27
Keating, John, Agent for Six family lands, Letters to (48) 1815-1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Six Family lands. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Keeler, James and Company, Quay Street, Albany, Letter to July 6. 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Mill stones for new flour mill on Conesus outlet. Bk 61 P 403 Shelf 27
Kibbe, William Cashier Ontario Bank, Canandaigua, Letters to (39) 1815-1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Banking business. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Kidder, Peabody Company, Investment firm, Letters from (4) 1877. Wadsworth,William Austin Investments; stocks and bonds. Box LWAW2 F 46 Shelf 26
King, Charles J Miller in Rochester, Letters from (2) 1841. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Milling. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
King, John Alsop (1788-1867) Governor of NY, Letter from 5/17/1861. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
King, Preston (1806-1865) Senator from NY, Letters from (2) 1848-1861. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Knapp, Florence, New York Sectary of State Letters from and to (12) 1927-1928. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Knapp, Florence; Her complaints about treatment. Box J112E F 18 Sh 59
Knower, Benjamin, Hat maker, 421 S. Market, Albany, Letter to July 25, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Sheep. See Also subject heading "Wool". Bk 61 P 133 Shelf 27
Knox, Seymour H (b. 1898) Buffalo NY financier, Letters from (2) 1928. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Airline stock. Box J112E F 1
LaFarge, Christopher Grant (1862-1938) Architect, Plans and Letter from October 22, 1907. Wadsworth,William Austin Gardener's Cottage plans. Box LWAW6 F 14 Shelf 26
LaFarge, John (1835-1910) Stained glass artist, Documents (1 folder) 1900. Wadsworth,William Austin Stained glass window for Homestead stairway. File Cab. 1, Drawer 2
Lansing, G G Oriskany and Utica Woolen Mills, Letters to (12) November 15, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; See Also subject heading "Sheep." Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Laurence, E Boylston MA, Letters (2) Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal; Art and drama. Bx LEAW1 Fs 27,29 Sh 23
Lawrence, Anson R Secretary Genesee Country Assoc. Letter from 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Genesee Country Assoc. Advisory Council appointment. Box J112E F 12 Sh 59
Legare, Hugh Swinton (1797-1843) Attorney General, Letter from 3/19/1842. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
LeStrange, Hamon W England, Letters from (2) 187i-1917. Wadsworth,William Austin Carriage order; World War I news. Box LWAW2 F 55 Shelf 26
Livingston Journal, Geneseo NY Newspaper, 1824-1828 scattered issues. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volume 3 Shelf 40
Livingston Register, Geneseo NY Newspaper, 1825-1828 scattered issues. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volume 3 Shelf 40
Livingston, Peter R. (1766-1847) Whig Senator, Letter to March 6, 1818 Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Master in Chancery; appoint Hastings to prove deeds. Bk 61 P 347 Shelf 27
Lodge, Henry Cabot (1850-1924) Senator and author, Letters from (3) 1881-1885, 1910 Wadsworth,William Austin Politics and personal. Box LWAW2 F 59 Shelf 26
Loebe, Sophie Irene (1876-1977) Nat Child Welfare Com Letters to and from (6) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Child Welfare in the Philippines. Box J112E F 5 Sh 59
Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (1807-1882) Poet, Letter to Fanny Farrer May 4, 1889. Wadsworth,William Austin Introduction for Mrs. Wadsworth. Box LWAW2 F 61 Shelf 26